hey guys this is um a new mod I found so
to show I haven't really done anything I
just started a new world I spawn there
randomly I I make I spawn with these
items though but I haven't done really
anything to this world and this is a mod
from the movie Harry Potter and it's
called quidd I don't know if you this
ball May remind you of it and so here
real quick this this basically when you
lay this it will spawn up the field it
may take a while to show it CU it's
loading and stuff but um you lay this
block and then right click on it and it
sets up the field now it's a little
laggy at first but you can see all this
land changing and wait for it just wait
it spawns up goals this is like the
coolest mod ever so you basically you
lay that block in the center of where
you want the field to be and it spawns
up Fields basically these are the goals
and I'll show you how to score and stuff
but see you try to score by throwing the
blocks in there there's broomsticks you
fly on and they try to knock you off and
take the ball from you and scored in
your goal and just so you got a clear
view see spawns gos on both sides level
with the block kind of you can see those
trees right there kind of got messed
over but real quick you have these These
are flags you can lay on the boundaries
of the
outside you have this little thing and
this and this this is what these are the
two things you use to play the game
basically capture and score with you
throw this block yeah it flies around
randomly like I showed you you try to
score with this one let's see if I can
make it yep and then here we go these
are the brooms you fly on now it's not
like normal flying oh that's a bit
laggy you lay the broom rooms see floats
you right click on them to get on them
and then at first C goes up and control
goes down but I switched it so my R key
goes up and my f key goes down and then
you move with normal Keys see and you
can go up and down like this and you fly
around and basically the goal is to put
the ball in the hoop you get a bunch of
guys I haven't really done this on a
multiplayer server but there's bats you
use and you walk and you fly around
smacking people and then it came with
its own custom jerseys and headband
which I mean if you got a you know four
on four going just lay that chest very
simple and easy on a multiplayer map
that ought to be epic cuz there's
different color jerseys and headbands
and oo it would just be so much fun I
can't imagine how fun this would be I
I'm going to try it soon and then you
just fly up and toss it in O short
I'm still getting used to it oh yeah you
saw my too many items
mod I'm
just but it's pretty awesome it's a nice
mod and I think that block right there
is what makes the mod so awesome like if
you had to set up this field every time
it'd be really annoying but since you
can just lay that block right there you
have your two gold post set up and then
all you have to do is put on jerseys if
you have more than one person and then
just toss random blocks and start
playing
it's so much fun and I just have fun
playing around by myself in this mod you
know but it's interesting looks like it
would be something worth practicing if
you start taking it serious I'll have a
link to it in the description so just
download it and give it a try it's
pretty fun all it requires is mod loader
nothing special download the mod and put
it in your jar file that's about it so
hope you like it